- I just bought this house, and I'm gonna give it to Chandler.
- Really? - No.
But, I am gonna give it to a pizza delivery guy, and here's how.
We ordered a pizza.
- [Woman] Domino's Pizza, how can I help you?
- Can I have a pepperoni? Delivery, please.
Then we paid a pizza delivery guy to help us move furniture all day.
We just need help moving furniture.
If we were to give you a few thousand dollars,
could you just help us move furniture all day?
- Sure. - Really?
All we told him is that we are YouTubers and we needed an extra hand moving furniture.
Because our friend Chad got laid off, and we really wanted to help him.
But little does he know, Chad isn't real.
At the end of the day we would actually
give him 100% ownership of the house
he is helping us move furniture into.
- Pranked! - Got him.
(electrical zapping)
- Surprisingly, he's going along with it.
All he thinks he's getting is a few thousand dollars.
After we move all the furniture in, we're just gonna be like, "This key is yours. "
All right, to Walmart it is.
(R&B music)
We're trying to just fill his house.
So furniture.
- So let's start in the bedroom.
- [Voiceover] Oh, baby.
- What do you think of a chair like this?
- It's assertive.
Oh, and it's got air lumbar.
Chad's lumbar do be needin' air.
- Good grief.
- Chandler, what do you think of this?
(knuckles rapping)
- Whoo-hoo, did you all hear that?
- Joey, can you give us the knock test?
(knuckles rapping)
- Yeah.
- See you guys, this is why we brought Joey.
He's incredibly helpful.
- I actually just bought my mom this TV.
- What do you think of it, Joey?
- It's a nice TV.
- Let's do it.
- We have a TV, we have a bookstand, and we have a chair.
Let's grab another TV.
This one has Roku in it.
I think we're good to go.
- He's our Domino's guy.
We just bring him everywhere.
(register beeping)
- [Tareq] Did you think you would be doing this today?
- No, I didn't.
- At all?- No.
- So the total is 2, 360 dollars.
Way less than I thought.
- So we got the furniture sort of done.
- Yeah. - All right, we got a U-Haul
for this stuff for Chad's house.
(cart wheels grinding on the ramp)
- Whoosh. - Ahh!
(door banging)
- See, this is why we brought you, Joey.
Throughout the day, anytime Joey told us
he liked something, I would go to a different aisle, and I'd call Jake and tell him.
Jake was in charge of covertly buying stuff so when we surprised Joey with the house,
we could have all this other cool stuff that means a lot to him in there as well.
- Jimmy's calling me.
Hey, what's up, buddy?
- Hey, so I rode with him in the car and I got some intel.
- Okay, what you got?
- I need you to get him the newest iPhone, a bunch of stuff for dogs,
and then he had a Monster sticker on his phone, so get him like a thousand.
Get him a thousand.
- A thousand? All right, you ready, Marcus?
We got it. - We got it.
- Let's do it.
- We got the Gravy bone.
- Hey guys, we got the cat food.
He said he needed cat food, right?
- He has a dog.
- Oooh. - What was he thinking?
- How are we gonna get a thousand Monster?
- [Marcus] Load it up!
- [Jake] Let's get all of 'em.
- [Jimmy] Very important intel, are you ready?
- Yes, we're ready.
- [Jimmy] He has a three year old daughter.
Get her lots of toys.
- Oh, perfect, thank you.
- [Jimmy] Despite the fact that you are like ginormous and scary, you'rethe perfect guy for this.
I'll be seeing you, bye.
- Bye.
Do we get her a playhouse, or do we get her one of the really cool motorized cars?
- You can't go wrong with getting both.
- Well, let's do both then!
- [Marcus] I think he'sgoing a little overboard.
- Driving blind.
- We're at store number two, some more furniture.
- Chris, this looks good.
- Leather?- Oooh, I like this.
(dolphin chattering)
- [Jimmy] How'd that dive feel? - [Chandler] It didn't hurt.
- I want both these.
- Oh yeah, this one's a lot better.
- This is going so well, he has no idea.
- Remember, right now he's helping us pick out furniture for his own house.
So what do you think about this whole thing?
- I think it's kinda cool
that you all are helping this man.
- So next up, obviously, we need a bed for Chad.
- Ohh!- All right, I want it.
(register beeping)
So far we're at $2, 400.
I wanna spend more money.
And that is store number two down.
Whoosh.
(R&B music)
- [Jake] $1, 400.
- [Marcus] Boy, that's a wrap. - And we still have four carts.
- Look at this receipt!
I hope they're happy.
They should be, we got a lot of good stuff, bro.
What are you doin' better not fall, boy.
- [Jake] Is that it?
- That's it.
Let's get out of here.
- We're now at US Cellular because we could not buy a phone outright at Walmart.
So we can surprise him with a new phone.
We're doing a video, and we're gonna surprise a guy with a brand new iPhone 11.
Everything here, it is cool.
Awesome, thank you all so much.
- So Joey's currently getting coffee, he took a little detour,
so we're gonna shop a little without him.
Before Joey gets back here, how do you guys think it's going?
- I think it's going good.
- He has no idea. - He has no idea.
- No, you think he'll cry?
- I hope so. - I might cry.
- I think he's gonna break out into tears.
- So you said you hadn't spent enough money yet, right?
- We've spent hardly anything.
- Well, you're about to drop a lot of money here.
- I dare you.
- We want the set of the May tags.
We can get this one, it's got a tablet on it.
- I blow hundreds of thousands of dollars on dumb stuff, but even this seems excessive.
- It's got a speaker in it.
- Never mind, that explains it, let's get it.
Hey Chandler, Chris is now for sale.
You're $799.
You were $1, 500 but you're on discount.
- [Chris] Yeah, it's because I'm kinda broken on the inside.
- [Tareq] So how much do youthink this total's gonna be?
- I would say $9, 000.
- We're at 55 with all that.
We gotta get a grill and a lawnmower.
2, 800 dollars.
(register beeping)
- Okay, your total is $9, 586.
- All the shopping is done.
Let's load it up and head to the house.
(dolly wheels bumping)
(R&B music)
(door banging)
All right, let's take it home for Chad.
(clock ticking)
- You're good, you're good.
Come on back now.
I'm scared, I'm scared!
That stopped just--
(glass breaking)
- Well that is U-Haul number one.
Oh god.
And that is U-Haul number two.
Now we need to fill the house up so we can surprise Chad tomorrow.
- Let's unload some U-Hauls.
- [Chris] What are you looking for?
- Some milk, man.
- [Chris] Why would milk be in the cabinet?
- There's no fridge.
We gotta put it in.
(dial-up modem beeping)- Oh.
- Go grab the fridge if you want milk. - Okay.
(cabinet door slamming)
- Dude, you got crumbs all over Chad's new counter tops, man.
- Good thing we bought paper towels and Clorox wipes!
(cookie crunching)
- This is a lot of stuff.
And I know we have Joey here to help,
but we still needed more backup.
So I brought an army.
Come on in guys, assemble!
Let's set up this house
so tomorrow we can surprise Chad.
(group yelling and screaming)
- [Group] Jake, Jake, Jake, Jake, Jake, Jake!
- [Jake] The box is breaking!
- [Jake] Where am I going?
- [Group] Pull, pull, pull, pull, pull.
- [Group] Push, push, push, push, push, push.
- [Group] Rest, rest, rest, rest, rest, rest.
(box sliding)
- We're bringing Chad here tomorrow at nine AM.
So we're gonna surprise him then.
We have to have everything ready by tomorrow morning.
Chris, you're in charge of the washer and dryer.
Chandler, you do what you wanna do, because you're Chandler.
- Huh?
- Let's go, people!
- What we have left is this beautiful fridge that I've been looking for my whole life.
This bad boy, 4, 000 watts.
It's got 20 lights in it, four cabinets, and a button.
Let's get it off!
- Do you wanna come back tomorrow morning when we surprise him?
- Really?
- If they drop this lawnmower, Chad ain't gonna be happy.
- There's gotta be some milk in this fridge.
For my Oreos of course.
- Oww, oww.
(plastic utensils clattering)
- Where's the milk?
Where's the milk?
My fridge comes with milk.
- Chandler, if you don't mind, they're trying to put the fridge in the house.
Please, just step back.
All right, go on.
So we low-key called back his store, and his manager actually drove out to the shoot
and he had this to say.
- So, we told you this story on the phone.
We ordered a pizza, Joey delivered it, and now he's just helping us move furniture.
So yeah, at the end of the day we're giving him this house.
- Wow, uh.
- So could you tell a little bit more?
Because honestly he hasn't told us much about his personal life.
- When the kid's off he works on side jobs all the time.
He lives in a place right now where the landlord's not too cool.
- Joey has to drive an hour to work every day.
And this new house we're about to give him is only 15 minutes away from work.
I'm just really happy that he needs it, and this will genuinely change his life.
- Smart TV, 65 inch, 4K, you know, ha!
- Da, da, don't hurt me!
Ahh, ahh!
- Get on the ground!
- Brush his teeth!
- I'm going to brush your teeth!
I will brush your teeth!
(low key music)
- Whoa, what is this?
Oh!
I didn't expect that to be in that many pieces. Um, somebody else's problem.
Marcus!
(low key music)
(construction banging and sawing)
- I call it, "Desk a la abstract. "
- [Jimmy] Oh my god.
You did that, that's you?
- I read the instructions.
They were in Vietnamese.
(hip hop music)
- It's been 14 long hours.
We've bought a house.
- We did.
- Which cost almost 100 grand.
And then we spent tens of thousands of dollars on items for said house.
- I spent almost 10 grand at Lowe's by myself.
- Thank you!
See, we weren't spending much.
I'm proud of you, you get a raise.
- Thank you.
- Joey's been following us around all day.
No idea, that this house is his.
We bought this house and he is going to keep it, forever.
It is his.
He's gonna walk through that door,
and I'm gonna inform him that this is in fact his house.
Let's do it.
Sorry about that interview, how'd it go?
- It was all right.
- [Jimmy] Was it awkward?
- Yes.
(group laughing)
- As you can tell, something's up.
We spent so much money on this furniture, that we can't even pay you
the few thousand dollars we promised,
because we put all the money into your house.
So yeah, sorry about that.
- Okay.
- Yeah, your house looks nice.
- Yeah, what do you think of his house, Jake?
- I think it's awesome,
I think he's really gonna enjoy it.
- What?
- [Jake] This is your house.
- Yeah, your house.
- Oh, we didn't tell you?
This is for you.
We were lying about Chad.
This whole house is for you.
Chad doesn't exist. - Wait, serious?
That is awesome!
- [Jake] You are Chad.
- Thank you!
- [Marcus] Yeah son, this is your house.
- So we noticed earlier that you had a Monster sticker on your phone.
So we bought you 100 cans of Monster.
- Wow.
- And then you said you had a dog,
so we bought you a bunch of dog food.
And some toys for him.
We didn't know which brand, so we just got all of 'em.
- Wow!
- [Chandler] We reminded you of your favorite thing.
- [Chris] Pizza.
- [Chandler] Pizza.
- Oh wow, there's more pizza in the stove.
Didn't even know that was there.
- Did you have any idea all day?
- No, I did not.
- No, you really didn't?
We were getting kinda worried because Jimmy let it slip a couple of times.
He's like oh yeah.
- I really didn't, at all.
It is awesome.
- Oh yeah, we got a couple of extra things too we should show him.
We bought some toys because you mentioned you have a daughter.
So we got her some toys too.
- [Joey] Wow.
- I know this must be I don't know her,
so I know, it's a lot.
- It really is, it's awesome, you all.
- It's all yours.
Like this owl, it's yours.
Do what you want with it.
You can just throw it.
- Just throw it?
(group cheering affirmatively)
Oh my god, this is awesome.
- All right, there's still more rooms.
We don't know too much about decorating, but we assumed this would be your room.
So you said you liked hunting, so we got you hunting things.
- Oh really?
- And here is the final room.
I know, just a bed.
You mentioned you have a PlayStation, so got some PlayStation stuff, and a Switch.
- Oh my god, you all are amazing.
- So we were talking to your manager out there
and he said that you are like an hour drive away from work?
- [Joey] Yes.
- So this will put you in only like 15 minutes.
- [Chris] Oh, that's great to hear.
- Oh yeah.
- [Jimmy] Do you wanna just say anything to the camera?
- These people, they're amazing.
Like my body is shaking a little bit.
- [Group] Oh my gosh!
- Yeah, it's bad.
- We literally tricked you into decorating your home.
- [Chris] Get pranked!
Would you have done anything differently?
- No, I like it.
I would never ask for anything like this.
The house we were in,
it was a horrible house.
It was very unsafe, and this house is honestly gonna be a lot better.
Safer for my kids, and better for our living.
We tried to get a house the day before you all gave us this house.
Honestly, I was going into this
thinking I was just getting a couple thousand dollars
to help move furniture.
Someone just really just gave me a house.
Now we can stop worrying about where we're gonna go from here.
This is really just a great opportunity for me and my family.
And I just want to thank you Mr. Beast for honestly answering all our prayers.
Because this is something amazing for me.
(group cheering and clapping)
- This is your brand new house.
Here is the key.
I actually lied, I did have the key.
It is yours, seriously.
No strings, no catch, no nothing.
- That's is awesome.
You mind if I give you a hug?
- Yeah, of course, man!
(group applauding and cheering)
And there you have it.
I bought a house, ordered pizza, and gave him said house.
Don't forget to follow meon Instagram and buy merch.
If you want to be entered in to compete in the million dollar series.
Goodbye.