- [Woman] What if someone sees?
- [Man] Nobody's going to see.
- Oh my God
Okay fine quickly.
- Okay.
(laughing)
That tickles, that tickles.
- Do you like it?
- I do.
(suspenseful music)
(phone ringing)
- Wait stop
My mom's calling.
(phone ringing)
- So just ignore it.
- No.
- Come on
so what?
- Okay Okay.
- Lilly where were you last night?
- Oh I was studying at Allison's house
I think she knows
(frightening music)
Hello?
Who's there?
(patting sound)
Mom?
Mom what are you doing?
(patting sound)
(frightening music)
- She knows what we did.
- How? I picked you up from down the street.
- I should have said the library
(knock)
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- Hello Allison? This is Lilly's mom.
(intense music)
(screams)
(scream)
- You want some
No one's going to know.
- Okay.
(Knock on the door)
(wind howling)
(suspenseful music)
(phone ringing)
Hello everybody it's your Auntie Paramjeet
you better like this video or I am going to beat your face
Comment below give it thumbs up and do subscribing
Last video over there, dumb vlog over there
you better make sure you coming back because we
making new video okay
one love whatever God stupid go to room.