Oh from that beautiful time of the year
that all you can hear in the hallways
these are you LeBron or you think she's
gonna say yes and of course every girl
is gonna be talking about one thing so
what are you gonna wear these guys don't
even go to our school last but not least
the ones who hate prom can we not go to
prom over it hey you wanna go to prom
with me oh my god yes
[Music]
guys it's the wrong girl don't take this
the wrong way but I heard one of the
guys say they want to take a goth girl
to problem shut up yeah whoo I think
it's that guy
[Music]
we wait no no I need to talk to you
about prom I don't approve you know I
don't wanna go to prom with you either
then why are you following me well I
want to take a lecture to prom and I
want you to help me take her oh that's
why you okay well not my problem
whoa whoa wait please I have to take her
to prom uh-huh mmm can you help me Oh No
or I'll thank you okay you know don't
take this the wrong way what why don't
you show you something sure I know
did you know about this yeah
you're dead like the squirrel in my room
can you just answer yeah under one
condition
what condition get closer closer
[Music]